Something's here! Watch yourself!
I know!
Son of a—
Kenzo!
Got it!
Each one of them is as strong
as an S-Rank hunter.
But...
They're still just magic beasts!
There's no finesse to their moves. Against
the versatile tactics we employ as hunters...
They can't win!
The ants down here are pretty durable.
Yeah. It's a good thing
there weren't too many.
Even if more appear, we'll be fine.
I'm backing you up from the rear.
You can relax!
Hard to believe you're the same guy
who was so afraid to go to battle.
You're one to talk, Yoonho.
What is this, your first time?
Otherwise you'd remember these things can
still move for a bit even without their heads.
You really oughta take their limbs out, too.
R-Right...
The further we go, the stronger they get,
but we still haven't seen
any of the bipedal ones.
Right. If I had to guess,
these came from a former generation
of queen's guards made obsolete.
So these are just the opening act?
Are we sure we're headed the right way?
We are. I think.
Seriously?
I wouldn't worry. I can smell
a powerful magic beast from further in.
At that kind of distance, wouldn't
President Baek be able to see them?
Fine.
There!
The queen's up ahead, in the deepest chamber.
She's got plenty of protection, too.
I guess there was a limit to how many ants
the diversionary force could pull away.
And among them are her personal guard,
each as strong as an S-Rank.
I couldn't tell how strong
the queen herself was.
This will be a tough fight.
But with this team, I know we can win!
Let's go!
Right!
Is this the right spot?
We came to check it out after losing
contact with Team Charlie, but...
Where the hell did they go?
They didn't seem to be having
any trouble with killing the ants.
Fujishima's glasses...
N-No way!
What's wrong?!
What the hell is this awful stench?!
I've never smelt anything like it before!
Have you been able to reach Charlie?
Not yet.
Did something happen to them?
No time to worry about that now!
Try and fight properly this time!
If I have to.
Well, well. Quite the reception.
We had better respond in kind, then.
Stick to the plan, people!
Get ready to light it up,
Mr. Ultimate Weapon!
I know.
You guys have to get past me!
I don't normally use this kind of firepower.
But today, I don't think
I can afford to hold back!
He's right. There's no reason to hold back.
As ugly as it might look...
I'm gonna slaughter every one of these bugs!
There it is.
President Baek's magic beast transformation.
It's begun...
We've got over 80% viewership!
Get further up so you can get a better shot!
Over 80%?!
I don't want to let them down...
We're in the boss room of an S-Rank dungeon.
Are you trying to get killed?
No! I'm sure it's...
Just stay behind me.
It's going to get even more intense.
And look at that!
The S-Rank hunters have finally
reached the queen ant,
and are battling even now
to accomplish their goal!
We've got S-Rank hunters
who normally never work together,
fighting in sync with incredible team tactics!
Hunter Cha's razor-sharp
attack pierces an ant!
It's down!
The last of the royal guard ants have fallen!
Now! Let's finish it!
Chew on these!
Without her guards, the queen's
just a big punching bag!
As long as I'm here, I can always get
the rest of you back on your feet!
You're not getting anywhere near our healer!
Keep her occupied!
She's still got this much strength left?!
Was that her death cry?
No... It's something else!
You won't escape!
Hold it right there!
Hunter Cha!
Miss Cha!
On it!
One last push!
They've done it!
Chairman!
Mission accomplished, eh?
It's... over now, right?
Seems like it.
With the queen dead, the surviving ants
will die out within a year.
And then people will be able
to move back to the island.
That scream at the end, though...
What's it matter?! We managed
to beat the ant queen!
We've avenged Eunseok!
I guess you're right.
Bad news!
The ants are moving back into the nest!
What?
The signal interference has lost effectiveness!
What's going on? Give me a sitrep, fast.
My cage of fire...  was broken?
What's going on here?!
We should still have time!
When the queen screamed just before...
She was calling for help!
Even then, the ants outside shouldn't be able
to break the Guildmaster's technique.
Then what...
We've got incoming!
A black... ant?
Between its spine-chilling presence
and this smell...
What is this thing?!
That's... no ordinary magic beast!
There's no time to hesitate.
We need to take it down—
It... ignored us?
Miss Cha!
Don't screw with us!
Eat this!
He snatched it out of the air?!
Surprised? We've got one heck
of a healer backing us up!
This is the skill I use to keep
myself safe: Camouflage.
It's able to conceal my presence
the way that Stealth does.
The downside is that
you can't move while using it,
but for a healer, that's not an issue.
As long as I'm here, my team won't go down!
No... Don't tell me that
even Camouflage isn't...
Byung-gu!
Yoonho... Run...
Yoon...ho...
Run...
Run.
You son of a bitch...
You are all... weak.
You have... killed... our queen.
Killing your soldiers...
will not make up for that.
Where is... your king?
A king...?
On the outside...
There is one... stronger.
Outside? Does he mean Goto?
No, I'll figure it out later.
We need to get out of here, now!
Damn it! The rest are back, too!
This is strange.
It's not just Charlie.
Now Delta isn't responding, either.
Could be a bad signal.
They should still be within range, though.
Bravo, respond.
This is Bravo.
Can you reach Charlie and Delta?
No, sir. We haven't been able to
contact them on our end either.
Should we investigate?
We're headed there now.
When you're finished on your end,
we'll meet at the rendezvous point.
Roger that.
How...?
It's me.
Why haven't you been checking in
according to schedule?
We've had casualties.
Well, that isn't good.
I thought you had been given the order
to only take out the evolved variants
in order to minimize risk?
They just weren't strong enough.
That's the kind of response
I'd expect from you.
Well, as long as you're there,
a handful of KIA is acceptable.
Incidentally, are our allies
seeing to the queen?
Yes, but the signal disruption lost
its effectiveness a few moments ago,
and I was able to confirm the ants
returning to the queen's nest.
And what would you say
their probability of survival is?
Considering the size of the force
they're against... zero percent.
Good.
Despite fighting their hardest,
our Japanese hunters
were forced into a temporary retreat
after our allies were wiped out.
In honor of their sacrifice,
the second strike team waiting at sea
will complete the clearing of Jeju Island.
A rival nation's military might is decimated,
and our country receives the glory
of conquering an S-Rank gate.
The timing is right.
All hunters, withdraw and rendezvous
with the secondary strike force in the fleet.
Fine.
Orders are in from Chairman Matsumoto.
We're pulling out.
We'll have to collect the bodies at a—
Ishida!
Go.
Head out to sea with Bravo
and prep for the next phase.
But, sir!
If you stay behind, you'll only be in my way.
Go.
Roger!
What a powerful aura.
Are you... their king?
A talking ant. Interesting.
The king... Yeah, I'm the king.
What is this magic power?!
I feel like... I've encountered
something like this before.
I think it was...
Choi Jong-in! Crank up the heat!
Don't be ridiculous!
This is as hot as it gets!
We're all hurt pretty bad.
Too bad to properly fight back.
And our last hope, Choi, is fading...
We're done for.
Who are these...
shadowy soldiers?!
Exchange.